Finding Aid for the Ojai Music Festival Records PASC-M.0277
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Business Papers, 1940s-1990s; Series 3.
  - S.C.E. Electric Bus Festival '93, 1993; Correspondence and schedules (Box 30, Folder 1)
    Related to Southern California Edison shuttle buses for the 1993 Festival
  - Samples from other organizations, 1993-1994; brochures, invitations, programs (Box 34, Folder 4)
    Sample invitations and programs from other art organizations
  - Santa Barbara Preview Music Academy of the West April 23, April 1995; In (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Santa Barbara Preview Music Academy of the West April 23, April 1995; invitations, drafts, correspondence (Box 32, Folder 8)
    Planning materials for preview performance
  - Santa Barbara Preview Music Academy of the West April 23, April 1995; In (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Signage Festival '93, 1993; correspondence and drafts (Box 30, Folder 16)
    Related to signs necessary for Festival
  - Silent auction, 1986?; papers, cards (Box 83, Folder 5)
    Bidding sheets for auctions; records of donation.
  - Special Events: Ruth Pash of Destination Resources, March 1995; brochures, correspondence (Box 32, Folder 12)
    information from vendor
  - Springfest, 1986--1988; papers (Box 83, Folder 4)
    Press releases, mailing lists, and planning information for Ojai's Springfests held between 1986 and 1988.
  - Stage chart Libbey Park, 1992?; maps (Box 39, Folder 3)
    Maps and plans for Libbey Park, including directions to Ojai.
  - Suggestion Box 1993, Comment cards (Box 30, Folder 13)
    Suggestions from 1993 Festival, from patrons
  - Thank you lists Festival '93, 1993; correspondence and drafts (Box 30, Folder 11)
    Related to letters to be sent to people involved with the Festival (eg ushers)
  - The Prime of Life Club (Yearly luncheon for the elderly), 1990s?; papers (Box 62, Folder 10)
    Information about potential locations and catering for the Prime of Life Club event.
  - Ticket Brochure, 1992-93; Contracts, correspondence, drafts (Box 31, Folder 10)
    Related to 1993 Ticket brochure.
  - Ticket brochures and information, 1991; papers (Box 72, Folder 2)
    Information about ticketing brochures and mailings.
  - Ticket Printers; Ticket Invoices, 1984-1991; papers, brochures (Box 74, Folder 1)
    Information and correspondence with various ticket printers with pricing and timing information
  - TicketMaster Sales and Records, 1991; papers, brochures (Box 72, Folder 1)
    Records of sales and transactions by TicketMaster on behalf of Ojai.
  - Topa Topa Travel--Travel Club (formerly Travel Time), 1986-1989; correspondence and drafts (Box 32, Folder 1)
    Related to tours operated by Travel Time for Ojai Festival patrons
  - Vendors (possible) T-shirts, pens, pins, bags, aprons, 1992; brochures, business cards, correspondence (Box 39, Folder 1)
    Information from potential vendors for the Ojai. For example, pricing information from The Apron Works.
    Includes program from 1992 Ojai Festival.
  - Vendors 1993, Correspondence and invoices (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Materials related to vendors for 1993 Festival, eg chairs
  - Vendors--phone, roof, phonebooks, 1991; brochures, papers (Box 33, Folder 1)
    Information about potential vendors for the Ojai Festival, eg Pacific Bell
  - Wine project 1993, Brochures, correspondence, artwork, contracts (Box 27, Folder 4)
    Materials related to commemorative Ojai Festivals Chardonnay sold to benefit the Festival
  - Board of Directors, Subseries 1.
    - Board lunch Festival '93, 1993; papers (Box 53, Folder 4)
      Mailing list, invitation, planning information for board lunch held at the Ojai Valley Inn on June 5, 1993.
    - Board luncheon, May 30, 1992; invitations, drafts, correspondence (Box 39, Folder 8)
      Related to board lunch, held at the Ojai Valley Inn.
    - Board of Directors Meetings, 1966-1967; Bound papers (Box 5, Folder 6)
      Minutes of Special Meeting of Board of Directors with receipt and disbursement records.
    - Board of Directors Meetings, 1967-1968; Bound papers (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Board of Directors Meetings, 1984-1985; Bound papers (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Board of Directors Meetings, 1983-1984; Bound papers (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Board of Directors Meetings, 1982-1983; Bound papers (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Board of Directors Meetings, 1981-1982; Bound papers (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Board of Directors Meetings, 1980-1981; Bound papers (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Board of Directors Meetings, 1979-1980; Bound papers (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Board of Directors Meetings, 1978-1979; Bound papers (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Board of Directors Meetings, 1977-1978; Bound papers (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Board of Directors Meetings, 1976-1977; Bound papers (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Board of Directors Minutes, July 1953-June 1954; Bound papers (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Board of Directors Minutes, July 1952-June 1953; Bound papers (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Board of Directors Minutes, July 1951- June 1952; Bound papers (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Board of Directors Minutes, July 1950-June 1951; Bound papers (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Board of Directors Minutes, Oct. 1949-June 1950; Bound papers (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Board of Directors Minutes, July 1963-June 1964; Bound papers (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Board of Directors Minutes, 1964-1965; Bound papers (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Reports to Ojai Festival Board, 1985-1987; papers (Box 84, Folder 2)
      Reports to the Ojai Board, submitted on behalf of the Ojai Women's Committee by the Committee President.
  - Development-- Appeals, Subseries 2.
    - "Other Boards" Fundraising Appeal, 1992-1993; papers (Box 61, Folder 8)
      Letters sent to members of other organizations' boards.
      Letters mailed March 26, 1993.
    - Board of Governors January '93 Appeal, January 1993; papers (Box 61, Folder 7)
      Appeal letters to renewing and new donors to the Festival.
    - Corporate Appeal Letter, February-November 1993; papers (Box 51, Folder 10)
      Letters and scripts for business appeal mailed on November 3, 1993. Includes names and addresses.
    - Earlybird and follow up Festival '95, 1994-1995; papers (Box 45, Folder 5)
      Mailing lists and plans for pre-Festival fundraising.
    - Event reservation forms, 1987?; cards (Box 82, Folder 5)
      RSVP cards and forms for two different events: one for the Ojai Women's Committee (no name/date provided), and one for the Fantasy Ball.
      No dates given, but the credit card expiration dates provided are between 1987 and 1988.
    - Fall Appeal '93 aka Corporate Appeal (sent 12/92), December 1992; papers, brochures (Box 61, Folder 12)
      mailing lists and cards for Fall Appeal
    - Festival '93 New Donor Cards, 1992-1993; papers (Box 61, Folder 11)
      Drafts of new membership forms and cards
    - Festivals Board Retreat 1998, Memos, invitations, brochures (Box 26, Folder 6)
      Planning and reporting annual board retreat of 1988
    - Finance '93 Concessions, 1993; papers (Box 52, Folder 9)
      Income information and records for concessions sold during the 1993 Festival.
    - Fundraising Events (Ideas for future), 1992; news clippings, correspondence, brochures (Box 51, Folder 11)
      A sampling of fundraising efforts by other Ventura County organizations.
    - Fundraising Ideas, 1996-1997; Papers, posters, cards, brochures (Box 26, Folder 3)
      Information from professional fundraisers with ideas; pamphlets from other arts organizations' fundraising efforts
    - Fundraising Ideas, 1996-1997; Papers, posters, cards, brochures (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Fundraising Info, 1986-1988; papers, brochures (Box 82, Folder 4)
      Information about other organizations' fundraising efforts, such as Cal Poly Tech's silent auction, as well as plans for the Ojai Women's Committee's Biergarten event.
    - Fundraising letters and mailing lists, 1989-1992; papers (Box 86, Folder 3)
      Copies of letters sent to potential donors; mailing lists; general fundraising plans
    - Fundraising special events, 1960's-1980's; invitations (Box 36, Folder 5)
      invitations for special events, such as the "Night of Knights" in 1964 program.
    - Golf Tournament, 1995; Papers and faxes (Box 25, Folder 5)
      Materials regarding potential golf tournaments to raise money for 1995 Festival
    - Grants E&O 1991-1993, papers (Box 62, Folder 3)
      Budgets and financial information for Education and Outreach
    - John Adams--Compact discs, 1993; papers (Box 52, Folder 3)
      information about distribution of John Adams CDs to donors of Ojai Festival.
    - June 1998-99, 1998-1999; Newsletters, invitations, reports (Box 28, Folder 1)
      Materials of the Ojai Women's Committee
    - KUSC Pledge Drive, May 11-22,l 1995; correspondence and drafts (Box 32, Folder 3)
      Relevant to KUSC (radio station) pledge drive
    - Member events and programs, 1991-92; papers (Box 86, Folder 2)
      Mailing lists, planning, invitations, and information about various member events, such as the Dickens Christmas program presented by the Women's Committee.
    - Miscellaneous Fundraisers, 1980s; papers, news clippings (Box 82, Folder 2)
      Flyers, plans, and news clippings regarding fundraisers, such as wine tastings and trips to the LA County Museum of Art (LACMA).
    - Musical tastings series, 1992; papers (Box 51, Folder 13)
      Correspondence, notes regarding musical lecture/tasting series.
    - NEA lobbying for continuation of federal funding, Spring 1995; papers (Box 45, Folder 7)
      Correspondence and plans for renewing grant from the National Endowment for the Arts
    - Newsletters 1991-1992, 1991-92; papers (Box 86, Folder 4)
      Newsletters (drafts and final) for members of the Ojai Festival.
    - O & E "Saddle Songs" Western Concert Libbey Bowl May 20, 1993, May 1993; papers (Box 61, Folder 9)
      Programs and planning information for community concert; donors invited
    - OFCOE--Fundraising Letter Feb 1993, papers (Box 62, Folder 5)
      Drafts of fundraising letters and ideas for OFCOE.
    - OFWC Party Mailing Lists, 1994-1995; Papers, cards (Box 26, Folder 1)
      Planning and correspondence related to the 1940's USO Stage Door Canteen Party
      Organized by Women's Committee of Ojai
    - OFWC Reports Special Events, 1996-1997; Memos, brochures, reports, press clippings (Box 26, Folder 5)
      Information relevant to Ojai Festival Women's Committee events and fundraising
    - OFWC USO Party, 1994-1995 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      Planning and correspondence related to the 1940's USO Stage Door Canteen Party organized by Women's Committee of Ojai.
      Includes one 3.5 inch floppy disk.
      Special equipment or further processing may be required for viewing. To access digital materials you must notify the reference desk in advance of your visit.
    - Ojai outings--O.F.--Art in the country, 1992; papers, brochures (Box 51, Folder 14)
      Notes and vendor brochures regarding Ojai Outings, a series of Meet the Artist tours.
    - Ojai Women's Committee, 1986-1988; papers (Box 82, Folder 3)
      Correspondence and information about planning by the Women's Committee, including the selection of honorary chairs for special events.
    - Opening Night Party Festival '93, 1993; papers (Box 61, Folder 3)
      Invitations and mailing lists for the Opening Night
    - Otis Chandler/ Brochure samples, 1993; papers (Box 52, Folder 6)
      Printing samples and payment information for brochure vendor.
    - Parties & Events, 1991-92; papers (Box 86, Folder 1)
      Invitations and planning for various parties/events, such as Arts & Flowers and the 1992 Preview Party.
    - Patron's Concert November 8, 1992, programs, papers (Box 62, Folder 9)
      Programs, invitations and information regarding a Patron's and Conductor's Circle concert in memory of Julian Spear.
    - Patrons/Conductor's Circle Concert April 18, 1993, papers (Box 52, Folder 2)
      Invitations and mailing lists for donor concert.
    - Peter Rawley Benefit April 22, 1993 Cancelled, papers (Box 52, Folder 5)
      Correspondence and mailing lists for cancelled benefit.
    - Post-Festival Appeal, July 1994; papers and programs (Box 45, Folder 6)
      Mailing lists and leaflets for post-Festival appeal, encouraging support for next Festival.
    - Potential Marketing Ventures, 1992-1993; brochure (Box 51, Folder 6)
      Brochure for Art of Miniatures retrospective held at the Carnegie Art Museum in Oxnard, CA.
      Note attached says: Hold in file "potential ventures" in development/marketing
    - Preview Concert, May 9, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 1)
      Invitations and mailings lists for preview concert held at Mr. and Mrs. Jack Smart's Residence.
    - Project 200 Luncheon, June 1995; papers (Box 45, Folder 8)
      Letters, invitations, planning for "Project 200" luncheon held on June 10, 1995 in the Ojai Valley Inn. Project in honor of Patsy Eaton Norris.
    - Proxy mailing and Fall appeal mailing, 1994; papers (Box 45, Folder 4)
      Drafts of fundraising letters and brochures; mailing lists; mailing permits from USPS
    - Robert B. Sharp Inc, 1992; papers (Box 51, Folder 12)
      Proposal, correspondence, notes related to potential sponsorship of Ojai Festivals by Robert B. Sharp Inc.
    - Singapore Airlines Proposal, 1992-1993; papers (Box 51, Folder 9)
      Correspondence and proposal to Singapore Airlines as potential sponsor of Ojai Festival.
    - Special events Guest lists, 1992; papers (Box 51, Folder 3)
      Names of individuals and corporations to be invited to fundraising/special events for the Festival.
    - Spring Appeal, March 1995; papers (Box 45, Folder 2)
      Drafts and plans for spring fundraising appeal, including mailing lists and design drafts
    - Springfest Reservations, 1989; papers (Box 82, Folder 6)
      Lists of names, addresses, and information regarding people invited to/attending Springfest.
    - Tracking '92-'93, 1992-1993; papers (Box 61, Folder 6)
      Membership tracking information for the 1993 Festival.
    - United Airlines Sponsorship Festival '95, 1995; papers (Box 45, Folder 3)
      correspondence and plans regarding potential sponsorship by United of the 1995 Festival.
    - United Airlines-Festival '93 Official Carrier, 1993; papers (Box 51, Folder 8)
      Proposal and correspondence to United for opportunity to sponsor the Ojai Festival.
    - Wine tasting scrapbook, 1970's; 3 ring binder (Box 46, Folder 1)
      Correspondence, planning, brochures related to the annual wine tasting held to fundraise for the Festival.
    - Women's Committee Board Meetings, 1999-2001; papers (Box 45, Folder 1)
      Minutes of board meetings held on behalf of the Ojai Festival's Women's Committee
  - Development-- Donors, Subseries 3.
    - 1992 Donor List, papers (Box 44, Folder 2)
      Report of gifts by donors, including individuals, foundations, and corporations.
    - Conductor's Circle--List of members (Plus VIP, FUND, Selected staff), 1993; papers (Box 52, Folder 7)
      Information and benefits for Conductor's Circle level donors.
    - Thank You Letters, 2000-2001 (Box 98)
    - Thank You Letters, 2001-2003 (Box 99)
    - Thank You Letters, 2003-2004 (Box 100)
  - Development-- Events, Subseries 4.
    - "Torch in the sky", May 28-31, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 5)
      Ticket order form and planning list for "Torch In The Sky" event.
      "Torch In The Sky" is a play written by Beatrice Wood in 1927.
    - Arts and Flowers Auction, May 1,1993 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      Invitations, mailing lists, correspondence for Arts and Flowers charity auction on behalf of the Ojai Festival.
    - Arts and Flowers Gala, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 2)
      Correspondence, receipts, and notes related to Arts & Flowers Gala held in 1993.
    - Board 96-97, 1996-1997; Memos, reports, drafts (Box 28, Folder 2)
      Materials of Women's Committee, including board meeting minutes, letters to donors, and event plans
    - Chamber of Commerce Auction, 1992; papers (Box 62, Folder 8)
      Invitations/letters and information about an auction to benefit Ojai Festival's Outreach and Education
    - Christmas at the Inn, December 1994; invitations, drafts, correspondence (Box 32, Folder 11)
      Planning for pre-season fundraising efforts.
    - Conductor's Circle Concert, March 21, 1993; papers (Box 52, Folder 4)
      Correspondence, invitations, mailing lists regarding donor concert.
    - Conductors Circle Events 1991-1992, papers, brochures (Box 81, Folder 1)
      Materials related to Conductors Circle (donor group) events, such as preview concerts and receptions.
      Includes sample invitations and mailing lists.
    - Corporate Breakfast, February 8, 1993; papers (Box 51, Folder 1)
      Correspondence, press clippings related to Ojai's potential collaboration with Amgen as corporate sponsor of a breakfast hosted by George Rathmann.
    - Day at the Races, 1985-1989; papers (Box 82, Folder 1)
      Flyers and information for various Ojai Women's Committee Fundraisers, including A Day at the Races, and Lucky Friday the Thirteenth.
  - Development-- Membership, Subseries 5.
    - Corporate Circle, February 1993; papers (Box 61, Folder 2)
      Invitations and mailing lists for the Corporate Circle membership program founded in February, 1993.
  - Development-- Research Materials, Subseries 6.
    - Community and Outreach, 1991-1992; papers, brochures (Box 81, Folder 2)
      Planning information for outreach programs; letters from schoolchildren in appreciation of past events.
  - Finance, Subseries 8.
    - 1993 Payroll Records, W-2s, 1099's., papers (Box 97, Folder 1)
      Payroll-related papers, including spreadsheets, photocopies of 1099 forms, W-2 forms, and related notes.
    - Accounting '93 Reports--Budget, 1993; papers (Box 80, Folder 2)
      Financial records--spreadsheets, memos, statemens
    - Accounts Payable '93 Independents '93, 1993; papers (Box 80, Folder 3)
      Financial records, including contracts, spreadsheets, and memos
    - Artists Withhold at Source 1993 #8109-1042 & 1042s, Tax forms (Box 31, Folder 4)
      Related to payment to artists at 93 Festival
    - Audited financial information, 1994; papers (Box 80, Folder 1)
      Financial statements; memos to/from Ernst & Young
    - Bank statements, 1996-97; bank statements in original envelopes (Box 3, Folder 4)
      11 envelopes of bank statements
    - Board of Directors Meetings, 1965-1966; Bound papers (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Board minutes and financial records
    - Board of Directors Meetings, 1975-1976; Bound papers (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Board of Directors Meetings, 1968-1969; Bound papers (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Board of Directors meetings, 1969-1970; Bound papers (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Board of Directors Meetings, 1970-1971; Bound papers (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Board of Directors Meetings, 1972-1973; Bound papers (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Board of Directors Meetings, 1971-1972; Bound papers (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Board of Directors Meetings, 1973-1974; Bound papers (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Board of Directors Meetings, 1974-1975; Bound papers (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Board of Directors Minutes, July 1954-June 1955; Bound papers (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Board of Directors Minutes, July 1958-June 1959; Bound papers (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Board of Directors Minutes, July 1959-June 1960; Bound papers (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Board of Directors Minutes, July 1960-June 1961; Bound papers (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Board of Directors Minutes, July 1961-June 1962; Bound papers (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Board of Directors Minutes, July 1962-June 1963; Bound papers (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Board of Directors Minutes, July 1955-June 1956; Bound papers (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Board of Directors Minutes, July 1957-June 1958; Bound papers (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Board reports '93-'94 Budgets, 1993-94; papers (Box 79, Folder 1)
      Board reports, budget statements; memos
    - Business records 1940s Ojai, papers (Box 14, Folder 4)
      Two copies of Ojai's Articles of Incorporation
    - Business records 1950s Ojai, papers (Box 14, Folder 5)
      Legal, financial, and insurance papers for the Festival
    - Business records 1960s Ojai, papers (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Business records 1970s Ojai, papers (Box 14, Folder 7)
      financial papers for the Festival
    - Business records 1980s Ojai, papers (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Check copies '96-'97 General Fund Outreach vol 2, 1996-1997; papers (Box 79, Folder 4)
      Photocopies of checks
      The first folder (vol 1) is in box 78.
    - Check copies '96-'97 General Fund Outreach vol 3, 1996-1997; papers (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Check copies 96-97 General Fund Outreach Vol I, 1996-1997; photocopies (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Duplicate Minutes of Board Meetings Some missing, June 1947, Oct. 1949- Sept. 1953; Bound papers (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Expenses Compensation Records '92 I of II, 1992; papers (Box 79, Folder 2)
      Financial statements and notes
    - Expenses Compensation Records '92 II of II, 1992; papers (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Festival '91 Accounting records Vol 1, 1991; papers (Box 78, Folder 3)
      Accounting records, including spreadsheets and transaction details by bank account
    - Festival '91 Accounting records Vol 2, 1991; papers (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Festival '92 Accounting records, 1992; papers (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Finances 1991 Artist/Production Costs, 1990-1995; papers (Box 81, Folder 5)
      Financial records for the 1991 Festival; lists of major donors through 1995
    - Financial Statements, 1961-1965; Carbon copies and originals (Box 6, Folder 8)
      Financial records for the 1962-1965 seasons
    - General Fund Cancelled Checks, 19991-1993 (Box 106)
    - General Fund Cancelled Checks, 19991-1993 (Box 107)
    - General Ledger, 1989-1990; Ledger (Box 37, Folder 2)
      Records of cash receipts and financial records for 1989-1990
    - Magee 1993, Faxes and correspondence (Box 27, Folder 2)
      Materials related to accounting dispute with Magee Audio Engineering.
    - Ojai check stubs, 1990; Plastic folder of check stubs (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Check stubs with notes
    - Ojai check stubs, 1990-1992; Plastic folder of check stubs (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Ojai check stubs, 1992-1995; Plastic folder of check stubs (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Ojai Festival invoices, 1994; Utility bills and notes (Box 2, Folder 25)
      Invoices for utility bills, with notes about payment
    - Ojai Festival invoices, 1993; Utility bills and notes (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Ojai Festivals Ltd. Treasurer's Report and Supporting Records 1964-1965 Season, July 7, 1965; Bound papers (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Accounting records for the 1964-65 season of the Ojai Festival
      Fred C. Embshoff, Treasurer.
    - Ojai Festivals, Ltd. Audit Fiscal Year 1956-1957 Copy No. 1, April, 1959; Bound papers (Box 6, Folder 11)
      Audit of Fiscal year 1956-57 submitted to the Ojai Board of Directors.
    - Ojai Festivals, Ltd. Audit Fiscal Year 1957-1958 Copy No. 2, March 22, 1959; Bound papers (Box 6, Folder 13)
      Audit of Fiscal year 1957-58 submitted to the Ojai Board of Directors.
    - Ojai Festivals, Ltd. Treasurer's Report and Supporting Records 1965-1966 Season, 1966 June 22; bound papers (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Treasurer's reports and financial statements for 1965-66 season.
    - Ojai Festivals, Ltd. Treasurer's Report and Supporting Records 1963-1964 Season, 1936-1964; Bound papers (Box 6, Folder 1)
      Treasurer's report and accounting recored for 1963-64 season of festival.
      F.C. Embshoff, Treasurer.
    - Ojai Festivals, Ltd. Treasurer's Report and Supporting Records 1962-1963 Season, August 28, 1963; Bound papers (Box 6, Folder 2)
      Treasurer's report and accounting recored for 1962-63 season of festival.